SURELY TOMORROW
'JARIM'S SON-IN-LAW,' CHO JIN-EON,
HAS AN AFFAIR WITH ACTRESS AN DA-HYE
CLOSE - SUBMIT
DONGWOON DAILY
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Good morning.
Hello.
What do you mean I'm not at work
when I just clocked out?
You know I worked all night long.
I even put the cursor
on the submit button.
Tell that idiot department manager
to just click on that.
And tell her that this idiot
assistant manager is at breakfast.
Has… the article been uploaded?
However, it is questionable to say
whether they actually helped
in reducing damage
or showed any physical measures.
The level of fine dust is worrisome…
Okay.
Our government and the US NASA…
The analysis says it is highly…
Assistant Manager,
the article on An Da-hye's been posted.
…up to 71%.
It was mostly influenced by Shandong,
which is in the same latitude.
Today, the Central Bank's
Monetary Policy Committee
set the fixed interest rate at 3.9%.
The economic growth rate
appears to be 2.6%,
which is 0.2 points higher
than three months ago.
As the economy is becoming stable…
What a great morning
to start drinking again
after I quit because of you, Seo Ji-woo.
It's hot!
Damn it!
Actress An Da-hye's alleged affair
raises suspicion.
The man involved
is the second son of conglomerate A.
The main issue
is the suspicion of An Da-hye's drug use.
I'll cooperate fully
with the investigation.
When An was taking drugs…
Seochang Group's second son, Cho Jin-eon…
Fuck off. Get that out of my sight.
- The prosecution is investigating.
- Cho's wife, Seo…
- Even to Seo Ji-woo…
- Seo Ji-woo's husband, Cho…
JARIM Apparel's second daughter…
- Seo has…
- JARIM's second daughter…
- Seo's marriage is…
- An Da-hye did drugs.
It could become an owner-level risk
for JARIM Apparel.
- Seo Ji-woo's JARIM Apparel…
- Seo Ji-woo is…
The public is paying attention.
Now that I've lived long enough,
I wonder how one's life
can be that turbulent.
I mean, why can't she just live quietly?
Why did she have to marry
a jerk like him of all men? Jeez.
You know what?
I yelled at my manager
that this is a current affairs piece,
not entertainment.
He'll end up at his father-in-law's
JARIM Apparel anyway.
How is this entertainment?
Am I wrong, Se-yeong?
Are you seriously asking me?
You need a top actress to blow it up.
He's just upset.
You really think he doesn't know?
Why ask if he already knows?
He just wants comfort, got it?
"I did my best.
It wasn't me who ruined Ji-woo's life."
This isn't the first time
her life's been ruined.
And she's firm.
Meanwhile, unsteady Kyeong-do
is pouring a morning drink.
Se-yeong, you know
I quit drinking when I was 30.
Why did you call us
if you're only going to talk to Se-yeong?
Hey, punk, because Se-yeong is
the most reasonable among us, you idiot.
- Are you saying I'm…
- Hey, will you shut up?
Are you going to drink?
Kyeong-do.
- Are you scared?
- I am.
- You want me to call her?
- No.
Don't you do that, Se-yeong.
And by chance, if she calls you,
don't give her my number.
You know that, right--
What's up with this timing?
MANAGER JIN HAN-KYEONG
Oh, it's the department manager.
Hello?
What? Okay.
Bye.
- You're leaving?
- What?
- After calling us all here?
- My work is calling me back.
I turned back from a business trip
to see you.
Gosh.
What?
I heard you had soju with your breakfast.
- So?
- You won't even have a beer with us.
- I'm disappointed.
- Didn't you hear? It was just a bottle.
Why order it if you won't drink it?
- By the way--
- No personal questions.
Please go to a sauna,
or at least the shower room.
You smell like a widower. Okay?
What is this?
Return to your seat
and enjoy watching
the surprised emojis on your article.
Okay.
An article on An Da-hye
made him drink soju.
Did you date An Da-hye?
I've seen many stuck on their first love,
but you're the only one
who couldn't move on for 18 years.
Am I right, Lee Kyeong-do?
You're making up a story.
You're not worried
about An Da-hye or her affair.
Stop it, seriously.
Did you drink soju in the morning
because you were worried about
the wife of An Da-hye's man?
It's humanism.
Hey, did you date Seo Ji-woo?
Use my title, idiot.
Assistant Manager,
did you really date Seo Ji-woo?
Have you ever bitten this before?
Try it today.
You know what happens then?
He'll write an article with his fingers.
Go to a sauna.
What is that?
- Go away. Go. Seriously.
- Okay.
Intern, aren't you going home?
I'm about to.
Yeah?
SEO JI-WOO
JARIM APPAREL'S SEO JI-WOO
SPRING, 2007
Hello?
How do I wait for an hour?
There's nothing but buildings here.
Oh, I don't know.
Call me when you're off then. Bye.
What the…
Where did it go?
What the heck?
What are you doing?
- I lost a 500-won coin.
- Just come already.
But I need that
for a banana-flavored milk.
Why did it have to be a 500-won coin?
Gosh.
Hurry up!
Damn it.
SURELY TOMORROW
EPISODE 1
JUWON UNIVERSITY CLUB FESTIVAL
All students of Juwon,
join the comedy club!
You over there.
- Me?
- Decided which club to join yet?
I'm not joining any club.
Okay.
Then why don't you come
and have a seat here?
Oh, it's an acting club?
Once you hear the history of Chaos--
I'm not into acting.
Oh, actually, neither am I.
Have a good day.
Not so fast. You can't just leave.
What?
Will you sit here just for five minutes?
Me?
Because I have to go poop,
and I can't leave here unattended.
Can you stay here for a second?
Well, that is kind of…
Oh, my stomach.
You know if I end up pooping here,
I won't just let it slide, okay?
But I'm just a passerby…
If anyone comes,
give the application form to them.
- But…
- Thanks!
Oh, I almost pooped.
If it's an acting club,
do you put on a play too?
Don't tell me… A newbie?
What makes you say "Don't tell me"?
Do you need a mirror?
- Fill it out.
- What?
CHAOS CLUB APPLICATION FORM
You just told me to look in the mirror.
I meant you look old
for your age, not ugly.
You're perfect for the lead role.
You have a weird way of talking.
NAME - LEE KYEONG-DO
Your name is Lee Kyeong-do?
As in latitude and longitude?
Journalism and broadcasting major?
Want to be a producer?
Are you a senior? Why do you talk like--
I got you one.
Is it ultimately about beauty?
I sat here for two days,
but I got nothing.
Beauty? Who?
How rude when we just met.
You dropped the honorifics to me first.
Get a grip.
Hey, why raise voices between newbies?
A newbie?
What? Did I say I was a senior?
No.
Then why are you making a damn fuss?
Bye now.
All right. Write down your number.
Let me catch her first.
Hey.
What?
Are we done now?
- No, no. Your email as well.
- What? Email? Email…
- Are we done now? Bye.
- Yes, thanks.
Good luck. I'll call you!
A make-up class?
Gosh, why are you studying so hard?
Whatever, I'm leaving.
I'll just see you in Apgujeong.
Hey, newbie!
Hey, but your school is pretty fun.
I'm hanging up.
Hey, since you were rude to me,
you need to apologize.
Let's face it. You look old.
I bet you hear that a lot.
It's the first time.
And who are you to judge me?
I was only expressing
what I saw and what I felt.
You're getting unnecessarily angry.
You're living in your own world.
Do you seriously think that?
You're laughing?
I'm bored. Do you want to grab a drink?
Hey, don't you have common sense?
So let's decide over a drink
if I'm clueless or if you indeed look old.
Hey, the sun is still high up,
and I have a class.
You're that upright?
A student studying at school
isn't being upright, but it's a given.
Oh, whatever.
Latitude, longitude, Kyeong-do.
Let's make a globe together in peace.
Hey, what's your name then? What's yours?
After the first toast,
I'll show you my ID.
By any chance, are you a light drinker?
Hey. That's ridiculous.
I could line up empty bottles
all the way to your house.
Want to see?
But I live in Busan.
Your hometown?
It's a lie, you idiot.
Let's go. I'll line up the bottles.
Damn it.
Cheers.
I'm Ji-woo. Seo Ji-woo.
What major?
Cheers.
English literature.
Hey, did you retake the college exam
three times?
You definitely seem older than me.
I've looked like this since grade 7.
This isn't Yonsei or Korea U.
Why repeat three times?
Jeez, you sounded like my mom.
You're so fucking annoying.
A penalty shot for you.
Too much?
I'll play along, kid.
It's sweet.
Excuse me. One more soju, please.
It's so sweet.
It's no use.
The school shuttle
has stopped running for the night.
Kyeong-do can't go home.
Do you want me to sleep with you?
Were you excited?
See you.
Gosh, seriously…
Shit.
Shit. That maniac, seriously.
- Hey, Mr. Kim.
- Gosh.
Go easy on the drinking.
- Okay.
- Can you tell?
Your booze smell's getting me drunk.
I'd fail a breath test.
What about your car?
My friend took it.
Anyway, what were you doing here?
You know Ha-yeong, right?
- Your friend from the US?
- Yes, her.
She goes to this school.
I was here to meet her…
Oh, but this school is so fun.
- Should I go here instead?
- What about your school in the US?
Oh, whatever. I'm going to sleep.
Newbie. Hey.
Oh, thank you.
Let's go.
What? Where?
- Do you live on your own?
- No.
- Are you taking a taxi?
Then drink more!
Let's go!
Come with us. Let's go.
Just go home, Woo-sik.
Why crash in the club room? We have homes.
And leave Kyeong-do alone?
Didn't I sound cool?
Do I look old?
You're helpless.
That's why he's with us.
What? Did someone say you look old?
Was it a girl?
No…
Do you think she's interested in me?
- But she said you look old.
- Yes.
Can you tell a girl you're interested in
that she looks old?
No.
Were you excited?
Shit…
Hey, where are you going?
Senior, where are you going?
Did you take care of the hangover?
Get out of my sight.
Let's go.
Go… Hey, go where?
The class is about to start soon.
- That's why we have to go now.
- Go where?
Hey, hey, but…
- Why are you doing this to me?
- I said, see you.
This is too one-sided. What do you want?
- Where did you sleep last night?
- Why care?
- We're not strangers.
- Then what are we?
We almost slept together.
What?
No. That's not true.
Are you out of your mind?
Maybe I am. You look handsome to me.
What?
If you keep acting up, I'll get mad.
You're so fucking cute.
Oh, can't you speak without swearing?
Where did you sleep?
I slept in the club room with strangers
because of you.
Did you join Chaos? I should join too.
Don't, or I'm going to withdraw.
- How many classes do you have today?
- Why do you ask?
Mind your own business.
- Let's drink.
- Drink?
Hey, I feel like throwing up
whenever I see green because of you.
I'll see you later.
When your class is over,
is it 5 p.m.? 6 p.m.?
See you in the club room.
Gosh, get lost.
- Stop talking back.
- Talking back…
Jesus. That…
Oh, I'm sorry.
Damn it, she ordered two.
All right, today, we talked about
how media affects our consciousness
when we view it as a medium
and a technical ecology.
By next class,
make sure to read Chapter 3,
Authoritarian Media Theory.
Yes, sir.
It's over, you prick.
Have the candy and go home.
Thank you.
Oh, you're actually loyal.
You're pressuring us.
Oh, drinking friends?
That's hard to resist.
Are you down for a drink?
- What? No.
- Then why are you here?
Well…
To become friends.
Shit, that's so much pressure.
What if your name were Wi-do?
Kyeong-do is better.
Why bother me smoking
when you've got nothing to do here?
I'm okay. Feel free to smoke.
How can I feel free?
Why don't you stop your fake cough?
Well… Where are the other members?
The three of us will do.
Sorry?
We got to secure
the club room again this year.
We finally have a newbie.
If one door closes,
another door opens, right?
When we were just about to get kicked out,
we got a newbie.
- Who brought him in?
- Right.
So are you saying if I withdraw,
you're at risk of closing or something?
Don't ask. It breaks my heart.
Hey, this is awesome.
We'll get to put on a play.
Hey, stamp the application form now.
Stamp with your thumbprint.
You were good at acting earlier.
CURRENT AFFAIRS
YOU'VE GOT A CALL
MOM
Hello?
Ji-woo, what have you been up to lately?
Well, I'm out to meet a friend.
This is why I told you
to stay in New York.
Did you come back to waste your time?
If you're going to take care of yourself,
do it properly.
I'm hanging up.
What are you doing here?
What are you doing? It's dark.
I'm listening to music.
Aren't you going home?
I will.
Get up.
Go first.
Thought you were tough. What happened?
You sorry for breaking your promise?
Did you wait for me?
Am I crazy? Why would I wait for you?
Then how do you know I didn't show up?
Well…
I had a club meeting. I had to be there.
Got it?
What?
Do you want to listen to what I like?
Whatever.
If you're not going, I'll go first.
Okay.
Gosh.
It's dark here.
The last bus will leave soon.
There'll be no one around.
So?
Get up. It's dangerous.
Are you worried about me?
Are you emotionally deprived?
Why do you keep
giving meaning to everything?
Wait, I mean, I…
Well, I was just…
Isn't my acting good?
- Aren't I perfect for the acting club?
- Jeez…
Oh, get a grip. Just get up.
The bus will leave soon.
I'm good at swearing, right?
Don't be proud of it.
Don't I look strong?
You look dumb.
I only practiced it to look strong.
You're so fucking annoying.
"So fucking" is all you can say.
I mean, do you want to look strong?
Yes.
What for with that pretty-ish face?
Did you just ask me out?
What?
You just asked me out.
I… I did?
How?
You just called me pretty.
I said you had a pretty-ish face.
I didn't exactly say pretty.
I was only encouraging you
to stop swearing.
If you say things like that
without meaning them,
you're a real bastard.
Wait up.
If I miss the bus,
I'd be sleeping out for two days in a row.
Oh, hurry up. There's no time for texting.
Okay, okay.
- Let's run.
- What?
What were you listening to earlier?
SUNG SI-KYUNG
TWO PEOPLE
After a long day
Under the moonlight, two people
Become one shadow
If I close my eyes
Faint happiness that I could catch
Is still there
A broken heart
May cast a shadow
Over your dream
But remember
That someone who loves you until it hurts
Is still next to you
Although this road
Seems too far
Although the sad heart makes you cry
Until everything becomes a memory
The two of us…
- Are you taking the subway?
- What about you?
I'm taking another bus.
Bye.
Do you have a cell phone?
Why?
Your cell phone…
Give me your number.
Give me your phone.
You don't look old. You look young.
Shit.
INCOMING CALL
SE-YEONG
Hey, Se-yeong.
- Hi, Kyeong-do. Where are you?
- Oh, I'm home.
What are you doing?
I'm just chilling.
Right, you should get some rest.
Did you get home safely?
Yes, sure.
You see, Ji-woo wants to talk to you.
No, never.
I mean, what's there to talk about?
It's not like I published that article.
I barely remember her face.
It has nothing to do with me.
I know. Yeah, you have a point, but…
Shit, I knew it.
I should've sent it
to the Current Affairs Team. Damn it.
Anyway, Se-yeong, that can't be done.
You also think that's wrong, right?
Yeah, I'm sorry,
but take care of it for me.
Yeah. Bye.
No, not me. What did I do wrong?
I did nothing. No!
Shit…
Hello, Dongwoon Daily Entertainment.
That's not our department.
I'm not sure. Maybe Current Affairs?
Yes, I'll connect you
to the person in charge.
Assistant Manager,
when did you go out with Seo Ji-woo?
What if she comes to see you?
How many years has it been?
Hey.
Well, I've heard that she visited you
when you were a newbie reporter.
Hey.
Hello, Dongwoon Daily Entertainment.
Yes.
Lee Kyeong-do?
Well, why are you looking for him?
Oh, you're his acquaintance…
But he's not available.
Business trip. Say I'm on a business trip.
He's on a business trip.
I'll let him know when he returns.
What's your name?
Jeez.
It was a woman.
Will you shut up?
It was exactly the voice
of a woman of Seo Ji-woo's age.
Will you go back to your seat?
- Okay.
- Damn you.
Gosh, so annoying.
OVER A THOUSAND RI AWAY,
I WILL DIE AND YOU LIVE
BOOK CONCERT FOR THE PUBLICATION
OF CHUSA'S LETTERS WITH THE AUTHOR
You call this a concert?
It is. It's a book concert.
What?
It's not too late now. Let's go.
Oh, it's starting. It's starting.
When Chusa was seven, he wrote
a New Year's banner to hang on his gate.
And Beonam Chae Je-gong,
who was passing by,
saw his writing and said,
"What an excellent writing."
As you can see, Chusa had
an outstanding talent since he was little
and was renowned for his calligraphy.
He also left many poems.
Oh, if you know
any of Chusa Kim Jeong-hui's poems,
please raise your hand.
- Yes.
- Domangsi.
Domangsi by Chusa. Bravo!
- Come on up.
- Go there?
Come here. You deserve a gift certificate.
Oh, yes.
Domangsi is also my favorite poem.
I actually proposed to my wife with it.
Thank you.
Do you like books?
No.
You looked like a Korean literature major.
I only like Chusa.
That poem.
- Was it Domangsi?
- Yes.
Did you memorize it?
Yes.
- Recite it.
- What?
- Here?
- Yes.
I'm curious. The title sounds funny.
What kind of name is Domangsi?
That's what I thought too.
I thought the title was funny.
But "domang" doesn't mean to run away.
Chusa loved his wife so much,
but she died first.
That's when he wrote this poem.
"Only if one could entreat Elder Wolha
that we be born
with fates exchanged in the next life."
"Over a thousand ri away,
I will die and you live."
"Then you shall know
the depth of my sorrow."
Wait.
Are you crying?
But why…
It's so sad.
What?
Hey, he must have missed his wife so much
to write such a poem.
I know.
Hey, by the way,
I guess you're not that much of a maniac.
Hey…
You're so annoying.
You scare me when you smile.
Just cry or eat me up.
Don't you have pride?
- You never change.
- What do you mean?
How can you be wearing my brand?
I got this so you'd thrive.
Is that a problem?
I'm thriving even without your purchases.
Sure.
Well…
What was that? The article--
I disappeared ten years ago
and finally showed up now.
Why would you want
to talk about the article?
I can see that you haven't been well.
How's your health?
Still the same. I'm exhausted
from all the psychiatric medication.
You still make me speechless.
Is it good?
I drink it 'cause it's awkward,
not 'cause it's good.
Or maybe because you're nervous?
Why don't you have a beer instead?
Ji-woo.
- Just say it.
- Are you sure?
- Want me to say what I want?
- Yeah, do it.
Godot never comes even if you wait,
but you'll come, won't you?
I've waited to see if you'd really come.
We're members of society now, right?
Why would you bring up a mere play
we did when we were 20?
A mere play?
Coward.
WAITING FOR GODOT
The name of the play is Waiting for Godot?
Yes.
Do you like plays?
I'm not sure yet.
Then why did you join the acting club?
- You're too pathetic to walk away from.
- You scared me.
Your arm is shaking so much.
Hey, hey.
You're the poop girl, right?
Poop? Did you poop somewhere again?
It's a misunderstanding.
Restrooms aren't just for pooping.
I know, but you said your stomach hurt,
and if you pooped there,
I wouldn't be able to get away with it,
and you ran away.
That's poop. That was definitely poop.
You really pooped. You always poop…
Hey.
Hold on. Are you the one
who got Lee Kyeong-do to join the club…
Yes, that's me.
Kyeong-do, you two argued nonstop,
and now you're dating?
Yes.
Too busy dating to come to the club room?
Have you memorized the script?
Are you performing? The lead role?
He doesn't have the lead role's face.
Whatever. Let's go.
The drink is getting cold.
Why would the drink get cold?
- Are you off to drink?
- Yes.
- Oh, no.
- Why not?
- Want to join us?
- Her eyes have gone crazy.
- Why are you getting excited about this?
- Let's go!
No!
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
MOM
Kyeong-do.
He's over there.
Kyeong-do!
Yes?
Speak casually.
Honorifics? That's all hypocritical.
There you go again.
You're the biggest hypocrite.
Se-yeong, what's your major?
Fine arts. But it's all hypocritical.
Art? Shit, tell it to fuck off.
Cover your ears. She swears
every time she opens her mouth.
Se-yeong, you're so good at swearing.
You should teach me.
Kyeong-do, you should break up.
She has a kind heart.
Have you seen it?
Gosh, have you opened her up?
You can see it without opening it up.
This prick is a damn hypocrite too.
How can you see it?
That's the poop talking.
- See? Your life is all about poop.
- Seriously! I…
If you're poop, I'm fucked up. I really…
Oh, not again…
MOM
- Don't you have to go? Let's go.
- It's okay. I'm fine.
What? Where do you think you're going?
We've only started.
I think Ji-woo has to go.
Oh, aren't you all going home?
We all live on our own.
You do? I want to be independent too.
No, you can't. No, no.
Oh, no. You'll end up like her. Okay?
What do you mean, you prick?
No, sorry. My neck hurts.
Come down. No! Don't! Stop it!
Will you stop fighting for goodness' sake?
Oh, stop it, please.
Hello?
Is this why you took a leave of absence?
As soon as you enrolled?
Mom, I don't want
to go back to that school.
Ji-woo, please!
I can't get anything into my head.
And I'm not interested
in Western art history at all.
You don't study because you like it.
You need a BA to get somewhere.
A proper degree.
So I'll go to a university here.
I'll prepare
for the college entrance exam.
Please?
Why can't you live with some pride?
What do you lack?
I got you everything you wanted,
but you can't stop taking
the depression medication.
Why…
Why is your life such a mess?
Read the room, please, Ji-woo.
Oh, my phone.
What's wrong? What happened?
I'm pathetic, aren't I?
For coming here with nothing…
I'm pathetic, aren't I, Kyeong-do?
No. Why would you be?
I'm happy that you came to see me.
I like you.
Ji-woo.
Do you know why I joined the acting club?
Because…
you were sitting at that table.
I actually joined the club
without knowing what it was for.
Because you were there.
I'm going to England.
Thanks to you, I'm free now.
Thank you for the article.
Just punch me, will you?
You still don't trust people.
Back then or even now.
I'm really thankful to you.
I got a divorce thanks to your article.
Thank you from the bottom of my heart.
He's claiming
I was at fault for everything.
Although I was at a disadvantage
from the start…
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
My marriage was more like…
Should I say M&A?
But I was the unfavorable one
since my youth was pretty turbulent.
They said I should be grateful
that they'd accepted me.
My depression and panic disorders
were also my fault.
Being unable to get pregnant
was also my fault.
I even heard about the rumor
that says I'm sterile.
We weren't in love anyway.
That asshole having an affair
wasn't shocking at all. But still…
I felt miserable.
Because he didn't even try to hide it.
Sometimes when he got drunk,
he swore at me.
Oh, that fucking son of a bitch.
Don't be like that.
You're melting my heart.
I can't fall for you again. Don't do that.
Will you get a grip?
How can you say that
in a situation like this?
That doesn't make you look strong at all.
I've been filing for a divorce nonstop.
And I finally got to end it this time.
Thank you so much. I mean it.
Okay.
If you say that, that's good.
- Bye then.
- Sit down.
What? Do you have anything else to say?
I don't know if this is exclusive enough,
but one more scoop so we're even.
No, thanks.
Oh, why do you have to fucking act up?
Why are you fucking acting up?
Write about my divorce.
I'll give it to you exclusively.
I want to look cool,
so make sure to say I've been filing
for a divorce for a long time.
Ji-woo.
When I had to confirm the article
about your hubby, I couldn't fall asleep.
Were you worried?
Yes, about seeing you face-to-face
and listening to your gibberish.
- Gibberish?
- Yes, gibberish.
Crazy gibberish, you cruel asshole!
See you at the funeral.
Whether you die or I die.
Is there anyone who can't make it
to the group blind date?
Raise your hand.
Why aren't you raising your hand?
Right.
You handsome ass must come.
Anyone else who can't come?
Oh, but I'm not…
Kyeong-do, it's this Saturday at 3 p.m.
I can't go.
You wanna end your school life, handsome?
I can't go because I look old.
I'd only ruin our major's impression.
I look too old. Sorry.
Hey, if you look old… Kyeong-do!
SURELY TOMORROW
- No way.
- Talk to each other.
- I'm not doing it.
- Don't do it.
- Work things out!
- Let's do it.
Kyeong-do's information
has all been released.
Seo Ji-woo!
The Assistant Manager idiot
provided articles for other media.
What do you think
of this ridiculous situation?
I was young, immature, and vulnerable.
I was innocent and sincere.
It was an 18-year friendship.
So don't make it look like it was love?
You got dragged into my mess
and almost had your life messed up again.
You're wrong. You got two things wrong.
I never got dragged into it.
And my life
had never been messed up before.